

CONTACT



sofiakasimiux@gmail.com



+31 687128060



SofiaUX/portfolio-website

SOFTWARE

ADOBE SUITE 🛍 🖪 🔟



SKETCH/FIGMA → F



BALSAMIQ

ATOM €

GITHUB (7)

LANGUAGES

GREEK

ENGLISH

DUTCH

GERMAN ●●



HOBBIES



ΓRAVEL







Sofia Kasimi

UX-UI Designer/ Frontend Designer

ABOUT ME

Creative UX Designer living in Amsterdam with experience in designing and developing real-world applications.

My passion is expanding worldwide by interacting with real-life use cases and get valuable insights for my design decisions.

Having applied knowledge in web front-end development, I understand systems and their limitations and can help to smooth the process between conceptualization and implementation.

EXPERIENCE

2018-Present O UX DESIGNER / ST-ART B.V.

Short term contract in a Start-up company

- Competitor Analysis
- Information Architecture (IA) of the app
- Prototyping (low-mid-high Fidelity)

2018-2019

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE / SOFIAUX

Frontend developer for Careerfoundry

- · Develop a responsive portfolio website with HTML5, CSS, JS by using Atom and Github tools
- Experienced in JQuery script and media Queries

2018-2019

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE / INKTANK

UX Designer for Careerfoundry

- Collaborated with high experienced mentors to design a user centered native app
- · User Research / User Personas / User flows
- Design interactive low-high fidelity prototypes
- Conduct Usability testing

2012-2018

O FREELANCER GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Logo designer & Book Illustrator

- Logo design accompanied with Brand Book
- Typography savvy in digital products



EDUCATION

2018-2019

CAREERFOUNDRY GMBH

UX Design / Frontend Development

- UX / UI responsive app from scratch with industry leading mentors
- Market research for user-centered product
- · Web app development using HTML, CSS, JS

2007-2010

VAKALO ART ACADEMIE

BA of Art / Graphic Design